<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addons>
<addon id="plugin.video.theismaili" name="The.Ismaili" version="2020.01.26" provider-name="JohnDoe27">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0" />
        <import addon="script.module.requests" />
		<import addon="plugin.video.youtube" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">the.Ismaili | The official website of the Ismaili Muslim community.</summary>
        <description lang="en">"The official website of the Shia Ismaili Muslims, a community of ethnically and culturally diverse peoples living in over 25 countries around the world, united in their allegiance to His Highness Prince Karim Aga Khan (known to the Ismailis as Mawlana Hazar Imam), the 49th hereditary Imam (spiritual leader) and direct descendant of Prophet Muhammad (peace be upon him and his family)."
        </description>
        <disclaimer lang="en">The content provided in this application is available free on public domain. I do not host any content. I am just providing the way to stream, All content is the copyright of their owner. The author does not have any affiliation with the content providers.</disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <forum></forum>
        <website>https://the.ismaili</website>
        <genre>"Ismaili,Shia,Muslim,Islam,Jamat,Jamatkhana,Aga Khan,Imam,Ismaili Imam,Hazar Imam,Mawlana Hazar Imam"</genre>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.tvondesizonexl" name="TV on DESI ZONE" version="2.8.29"
	provider-name="ajdeveloped/jchirag/johndoe27">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.19.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.simplejson" />
		<import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" />
		<import addon="script.module.elementtree" />
		<import addon="script.module.resolveurl" version="5.0.0" />
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="main.py">
	<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary>Watch Indian TV videos as seen on desirulez.net</summary>
		<description>Watch Indian TV videos as seen on desirulez.net</description>
		<disclaimer>This addon makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and
			hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without
			limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability,
			fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual
			property or other violation of rights. Further, TV on DESI ZONE addon
			does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy,
			likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on the
			Internet web site where from data is retrieved or otherwise relating
			to such materials or on any sites linked to this addon. Videos are
			basically links from video-hosting website that are having full rights to
			remove such access to video if required. Videos are nor owned or uploaded by
			ajdeveloped, the addon parses the content of a website and hows it in form
			of lists. The websites that are parsed by this add-on are not owned or maintained by
			ajdeveloped. This addon acts like a browser not content(video or link) provider.
		</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GPL v3</license>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.desiaddon" name="[B][COLOR yellow]Desi Add-Ons[/COLOR][/B]" version="1.2.0" provider-name="johndoe27">
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="DESI ADD-ONs">
		<dir>
			<info compressed="false">https://github.com/johndoe27/timepass-projects/raw/master/addons.xml</info>
			<checksum>https://github.com/johndoe27/timepass-projects/raw/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
			<datadir zip="true">https://github.com/johndoe27/timepass-projects/raw/master/zips/</datadir>
		</dir>

		<dir>
        <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jsergio123/zips/master/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jsergio123/zips/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jsergio123/zips/master/</datadir>
		</dir>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary>Source to install all DESI ADD-ONs</summary>
		<description>Enjoy access to Indian media sources. All add-ons provide access to website like a normal browser.</description>
		<disclaimer>The video add-ons hosted by my Johndoe27 makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, video add-ons don't warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on the Internet web site where from data is retrieved or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this addon. Videos are streamed directly from video-hosting websites that are having full rights to remove such access to video if required. These add-ons access website contents like a normal web browser and show content to users.</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>
</addons>
